what UPS coppice I share it on Twitter
what up guys so we have an announcement
to make today
or for my 4th well will hide you for now
maybe uh - where do you want to be out
your desk can you introduce yourself to
the Skokie's so welcome to the new kalbi
we've moved the cabbie into here what -
secret prototype yeah I mean it's kind
of like kind of vaguely visible in the
okay we won't talk about it all the
sales numbers are you'll see all right
Toronto announced do you want to uh
introducing our new employee
let's go peace do you guys know what
this is no I don't know
so EPS 2019 huh call him the when moon
nope this is not the new ml guy nope
it's not Obama
oh yeah BG that's right oh I believe I
believe he goes by Nick now and he's
next to all of the beautiful fulfillment
stuff so when you buy something on shop
comment on AI yes we have stock and
we'll ship it out he is handsome you got
a compliment
yeah that's a first yeah so what we're
also doing today is the naming challenge
so do you want to introduce the naming
challenge yeah we got 3d printers today
all right installed today setup today so
we've named them
we have print emic print face Donald for
Donald Glover and this one's blank so we
needs best suggestions no peace come up
with the name for the printer nice or
traps to sort X M 100 it matches uh all
the others or tracks at 100 s say all of
names just get an industrial laser 3d
printer Y filament BS tweet me an
industrial laser 3d printer oh you get
love alright so guys yeah we do need to
be doing the name here for this printer
all 3d printer with the B that's a
pretty good meme that's a good that's a
good meme yeah I know about dole dippers
never name the printer chase okay we're
gonna we're gonna put a vote on slack
yes and we will honestly take your
advice so if you brigade the vote and
you want to name it North Korea that's
okay show for your vote she'll she'll
for your vote that's it that's all we
have to talk about on this Kofi we're
gonna get that on slack I'm gonna post
it on comma get your votes in pulp the
garage door e 11 millions all right all
right get those suggestions on slack
what products do we produce oh we go
through the products
so we produced Wow many promise oh this
is the new GPU computer by the way it's
GPU slave double zero you have to run
quiet Sh
no no no no this fan blows outside guys
no accord yet so these are our products
we have 64 gigabyte eons
I love the beaming we have 128 gig eons
oh wait no we don't those are out of
stock and we have midnight black eons we
have grey pandas in various states of
production we have Palace we don't
produce them here
pandas are made externally but you can
buy a panda at shop that common today I
for only $99 maybe even on Amazon soon
we're gonna pull a Kanye West oh you
know how Kanye said his music was only
gonna be on tidal um what are you up to
what are you doing just finish it
another prayers yeah print up some
shelves from a storage giraffes and gray
pandas and powers and debug boards this
maze is the common trademark infringing
space one day China will find out what
we're up to
we'll have to rename it yeah we use GPUs
in-house we don't use GPUs in the cloud
is karma a school project yes yes I hope
I get class credit
pen holy cannoli I'm not really a pen
student this girl who I'm madly in love
with and I broke into pen holy last year
but now she doesn't talk to me anymore
she got a real job and thinks I'm a bad
influence
it's too honest on the scobie's alright
honestly our you can only trust garbage
with this year we like a sure do you
sell your know-how no no I'm not gonna
sell out man I learned that I'm a punk
don't sell out can you ever talk
[Laughter]
you can apply give me a Java comma a I
why did we break up she got a job she
wanted to be a real functioning member
of society unlike me she thinks I'm a
bad influence when I talk about how
societies a scam but it is guys can you
be the floor sweeper we already hired
someone for that it's the Roomba um
common guys probably a scam probably I
decided I was honest with you guys on
once Kelpie no but like it Scott like
the thing is if it is a scam it's an
ethical scam because we're very
transparent with you maybe one day I'll
find out it was a scam and I'll be like
damn why do I work on a scam all those
years but uh yeah yeah yeah alright
alright scope is I get on that that 3d
printer naming oh how do you know he is
working at comma I think he starts in
July um you're too transparent no
company should have scopes okay all
right you know you got you are right no
more scopes this is the last one cares
man
that's the best thing about winning is
even better when you tell your opponents
what you're doing every step of the way
and still win name your printer Ford
Fusion that's true we won't have a ford
fusion anymore when moon I bought bit
Kinect and I lost money yes we're very
excited about Southtown joining us to
work on
this is here and we're not gonna tell
you what it is but there's a lot of them
in these boxes what I think way my
waiting is self-driving the race
unlikely I'm greeting over a bit connect
neither put a bra you guys ones or
attracts boxes so good chase has the
most votes I'd slack is there a vote one
vote can you vote for anything bud chase
Oh chase it I don't know if you could
vote for yourself Chase has one thumbs
down that's true that's that that Roy
more guy showed up on a horse to vote
for himself all right a maximum we use
vim we were trying to ship Emacs in the
next neo ass but it was too large so we
had to take it out you'll accomplish it
all right later guys